8000 BC
Ice Age Plain
3000 BC
Primeval Forest
1000 BC
First Fishers
200 BC
Germanic Settlement
Abandoned
The Sprevane
The Fishing Village
The Stronghold
The Ford
The Margrave
German Settlers
Cölln
Berlin
The Twin Towns
United
Brick Gothic
The Great Fire
Rebuilt in Brick
The Elector's Castle
The Residence
The Chapel
Gothic Complete
Renaissance
The Lustgarten
Prosperity
War Begins
Plague and Occupation
Peace
The Great Elector
The Huguenots
The Arsenal
Schlüter Begins
Kingdom of Prussia
The Baroque Palace
Frederick the Great
The First Cathedral
Enlightenment
The Gate
Napoleon
The Quadriga Returns
Schinkel
Revolution
The Dome
The Empire
Gründerzeit
Cleared
The Cathedral
Electric
War Begins
The Republic
Weimar
Golden Twenties
The Flags
The Games
War Again
Burning
Ruins
Clearing
Demolition
Marx-Engels-Platz
The Wall
The Tower
Palace of the Republic
Everyday
The Wall Falls
Reunification
Closed
Stripped
Empty Again
Rebuilding
The Palace Returns
Present Day
Green City
High Water
The Last Frame